[
    {
        "question": "و ي ل ي ا م",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "ز و ر و",
        "response": "زورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ل و ف ي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ي ر ي ن",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ا ه ي ت و",
        "response": "ماهيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ه م ت ا ر و",
        "response": "همتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ل و ي ف ي ا",
        "response": "الويفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن و ي ل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ا ي ل ي",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ب ا ن ك ا ي",
        "response": "بانكاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ل ا و",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ا د ا ر ا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي و ر ي ت ش ي",
        "response": "يوريتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ي ت ا ت ش ي",
        "response": "ايتاشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت و ب ي",
        "response": "توبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن و ب ا ر ا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "غ و ج و",
        "response": "غوجو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ه ا ش ي ر ا م ا",
        "response": "هاشيراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "ب و ر و ت و",
        "response": "بوروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي و س و ب",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ي م",
        "response": "ريم"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا ش ي س و ي",
        "response": "اوتشيها شيسوى"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ي د",
        "response": "كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ي ك ا س ا",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "د ا ن ز و",
        "response": "دانزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "و ي ن غ",
        "response": "وينغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ي ن ش ي ه ا ن",
        "response": "تينشيهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "غ و ك و",
        "response": "غوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غ ي و",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ج ي ر ا ي ا",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ا ز ي ك ا ج ي",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك و ك و م ي",
        "response": "كوكومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غ ي ت و",
        "response": "غيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ش ي و",
        "response": "تشيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "س ا س و ر ي",
        "response": "ساسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن ي ز و ك و",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ي د و ر ي ا",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ن ي ج ي",
        "response": "نيجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا س ت ا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ل ي ز ا",
        "response": "ليزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك ا غ و ي ا",
        "response": "كاغويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ه ي ن ا",
        "response": "هينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ل و ك ا",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ه ي ن ا ت ا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ز ي ن ت س و",
        "response": "زينتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ي ن غ و ك و",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ل ي ف ا ي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ك و ر ت ا",
        "response": "كورتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ه ي س و ك ا",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
       "question": "ل ا ي ت",
        "response": "لايت"
    },
    {
       "question": "ب ي ا ك و غ ا ن",
        "response": "بياكوغان"
    },
    {
       "question": "ش و ك و",
        "response": "شوكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "د ي ك و",
        "response": "ديكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ي ا م ي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ف ا ن ج ا ن س",
        "response": "فانجانس"
    },
    {
       "question": "ي و ل ي و س",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "ت س و م و غ و",
        "response": "تسوموغو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ن ا ن ا م ي",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ا ي ز ن",
        "response": " ايزن"
    },
    {
       "question": "ز ا ر ا ك ي",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ا و ر ا ه ا ر ا",
        "response": "اوراهارا"
    },
    {
       "question": "ا ي ن و ي",
        "response": "اينوي"
    },
    {
       "question": "غ و ه ا ن",
        "response": "غوهان"
    },
    {
       "question": "ك ي ر ي ل ي ن",
        "response": "كيريلين"
    },
    {
       "question": "ه ي ن ا ت س و ر ",
        "response": "هيناتسور"
    },
    {
       "question": "ر ي ت ش ي ل ",
       "response": "ريتشيل"
    },
    {
       "question": "س و ك و ن ا ",
       "response": " سوكونا"
}
]
